<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>The Polytechnic Documentation</title><link>https://thepoly.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on The Polytechnic Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://thepoly.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Covered Topics</title><link>https://thepoly.github.io/docs/opinion/covered-topics/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://thepoly.github.io/docs/opinion/covered-topics/</guid><description>Covered Topics Here are the polytechnic Covered Topics</description></item><item><title>Fact-checking guide</title><link>https://thepoly.github.io/docs/copy/fact-checking-guide/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://thepoly.github.io/docs/copy/fact-checking-guide/</guid><description>What is second reading? At The Poly, an article goes through three different readers. The first reader of an article is the one who checks for readability, grammar, and structure. It is the responsibility of the person that second reads to fact check everything in the article. If a person is referenced, a sports team or statistic mentioned, everything about the referenced fact must be correct. Mistakes and inaccuracies in articles undermine the public’s trust in our organization and should be prevented.</description></item><item><title>How to Write an Opinion Piece</title><link>https://thepoly.github.io/docs/opinion/how-to-write-an-opinion-piece/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://thepoly.github.io/docs/opinion/how-to-write-an-opinion-piece/</guid><description>How to Write an Opinion Piece Here are the polytechnic How to Write an Opinion Piece</description></item><item><title>Kicker List</title><link>https://thepoly.github.io/docs/copy/kicker-list/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://thepoly.github.io/docs/copy/kicker-list/</guid><description>Kickers Kickers are displayed at the top of every article, above the headline. Their purpose is to give the reader a glimpse of what the article will touch on. This is a list of the kickers we've used—if it's not in all caps, it's not a kicker—and the contexts in which they're appropriate.
News STUDENT SENATE EXECUTIVE BOARD RENSSELAER UNION Director of the Union search ADMINISTRATION Judicial inquiries Safe Alert STUDENT RIGHTS Handbook updates Events ON-CAMPUS EVENT POLITICAL EVENT Administration Save the Union COMMUNITY EVENT Town meeting GUEST SPEAKER CIA director SCOTUS justice INTERVIEW Rick Hartt TOWN MEETING President’s Fall, Spring STUDENT ACTIVISM ACTIVISM INCLEMENT WEATHER GREEK LIFE GM WEEK [YEAR] CAMPUS SECURITY FRESHMAN ELECTIONS TRANSPORTATION JUDICIAL BOARD DECISION ELECTIONS THE ARCH Features Events CULTURAL EVENT Holi, the fashion show, drag shows STUDENT PERFORMANCE For events that don’t require participation, like RPI Players, cultural dances, and Sheer Idiocy.</description></item><item><title>Movie Review Guide</title><link>https://thepoly.github.io/docs/features/movie-review-guide/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://thepoly.github.io/docs/features/movie-review-guide/</guid><description>Movie Review Guide Here are the polytechnic Movie Review Guide</description></item><item><title>Protest Guide</title><link>https://thepoly.github.io/docs/news/protest-guide/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://thepoly.github.io/docs/news/protest-guide/</guid><description>Protest Guide Here are the polytechnic Protest Guide</description></item><item><title>Student Government</title><link>https://thepoly.github.io/docs/news/student-government/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://thepoly.github.io/docs/news/student-government/</guid><description>Student Government Here are the polytechnic Student Government</description></item><item><title>Style Guide</title><link>https://thepoly.github.io/docs/copy/style-guide/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://thepoly.github.io/docs/copy/style-guide/</guid><description>The Polytechnic Style Guide Updated 11/14/2019 at 2:21 pm. That's &amp;ldquo;mm/dd/yyyy,&amp;rdquo; by the way.
How to use this guide This guide is built to be as easily accessed as possible. Words in italics are used to show example usage, and e.g. means &amp;ldquo;for example.&amp;rdquo;
15th Street footbridge Use the 15th Street footbridge on the first reference and the footbridge on subsequent references. Footbridge should be lowercase.
24-hour This construction is an adjective, so hyphenate it.</description></item><item><title>Writing Basics</title><link>https://thepoly.github.io/docs/news/writing-basics/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://thepoly.github.io/docs/news/writing-basics/</guid><description>Writing Basics Here are the polytechnic Writing Basics</description></item></channel></rss>